Last updated: April 2023

DISCOVERY EDUCATIONDATA PROCESSING ADDENDUM

This Data Processing Addendum, including its Schedules, (“DPA”) forms part of the Standard Terms of Serviceand License (the “Agreement”) between Discovery Education Europe Limited and its Affiliates (collectively,“Discovery Education”) and the subscriber to the relevant Discovery Education Services (“Subscriber”) toreflect the Parties’ agreement with respect to the Processing of Subscriber Data. Discovery Education andSubscriber are each referred to herein as a “Party” and collectively as the “Parties.”

Except where the context requires otherwise, references in this DPA to the Agreement are to the Agreement asamended by, and including, this DPA. Except as modified below, the terms of the Agreement shall remain in fullforce and effect.

1. Definitions and Interpretation

1.1 In this DPA, the following terms shall have the meanings set out below and cognate terms shall beconstrued accordingly:

“Affiliates” means, any person, corporation, company, partnership, joint venture, or other entitycontrolling, controlled by, or under common control with the applicable Party. For such purpose, theterm “control” means the holding of 50% or more of the common voting stock or ordinary shares in, orthe right to appoint 50% or more of the directors of, the corporation, company, partnership, joint venture,or entity.

“Account Data” means Personal Data that relates to Subscriber’s relationship with Discovery Education,including to access Subscriber’s account and billing information, identity verification, maintain orimprove performance of the Services, provide support, investigate and prevent system abuse, or fulfilllegal obligations.

“Applicable Data Protection Laws” means applicable laws relating to privacy and/or data protection,which are applicable to either Party. It shall include without limitation and as applicable (i) the EU e-Privacy Directive 2002/58/EC as implemented by countries within the European Economic Area(“EEA”); (ii) the EU General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“GDPR”) as implemented bycountries within the EEA; (iii) the UK Data Protection Act 2018, the UK Privacy and ElectronicCommunications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, and the GDPR as retained as UK law by the EuropeanUnion (Withdrawal) Act 2018 (“UK GDPR”); (iv) the Swedish Data Protection Act (2018:218); and (v)other laws, rules and regulations that are similar, equivalent to, or successors to the laws that are identifiedin (i) through (iv) above.

“Restricted Transfer” means (a) a transfer of Subscriber Data from or which originated in the EEA toa country outside of the EEA that is not considered to provide an “adequate level” of data protection bythe European Commission and where such transfer is subject to the GDPR (“EEA Restricted Transfer”)and (b) a transfer of Subscriber Data from or which originated in the UK to a country outside of the UKthat is not considered to provide an “adequate level” of data protection by the UK Government and wheresuch transfer is subject to the UK GDPR (“UK Restricted Transfer”).

“Services” means the services and other activities to be supplied to or carried out by or on behalf ofDiscovery Education for Subscriber pursuant to the Agreement.

“Standard Contractual Clauses” means the Standard Contractual Clauses for the transfer of PersonalData to Third Countries set out in Commission Implementing Decision (EU) 2021/914 of 4 June 2021on standard contractual clauses for the transfer of personal data to third countries pursuant to Regulation(EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council and available at https://eur-lex.europa.eu/eli/dec_impl/2021/914/oj?uri=CELEX%3A32021D0914\&locale=e.

“Subscriber Data” means any Personal Data Processed by Discovery Education in connection with theprovision of Services to Subscriber.

“UK Addendum” means the International Data Transfer Addendum to the EU Commission StandardContractual Clauses (the Standard Contractual Clauses defined above) issued by the Commissioner under

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

2

S119A(1) Data Protection Act 2018, Version B1.0, in force 21 March 2022 and available

at https://ico.org.uk/media/for-organisations/documents/4019539/international-data-transfer-addendum.pdf.

1.2 The terms “Controller,” “Data Subject,” “Personal Data,” “Processor,” and “Processing” have themeanings given to them in Applicable Data Protection Law(s). If and to the extent that Applicable DataProtection Law(s) does not define such terms, then the definitions given in GDPR will apply.

1.3 All terms not defined herein will have the same meaning as set forth in the Agreement or the ApplicableData Protection Laws.

2. Role and Scope of Processing

2.1 Scope. This DPA will apply only to the extent that Discovery Education Processes Subscriber Data, onbehalf of Subscriber, to which Applicable Data Protection Laws apply.

2.2 Details of Processing. The details of Discovery Education’s Processing of Subscriber Data are describedin Schedule 1 to this DPA.

2.3 Discovery Education as a Processor. The parties acknowledge and agree that regarding the Processingof Subscriber Data, Discovery Education is a Processor. Discovery Education will Process SubscriberData in accordance with Subscriber’s instructions as set forth in Section 3 (Subscriber Instructions).

2.4 Discovery Education as a Controller of Account Data. The parties acknowledge that, regarding theProcessing of Account Data, Subscriber is a controller and Discovery Education is an independentcontroller, not a joint controller with Subscriber. Discovery Education will Process Account Data as acontroller (a) in order to manage the relationship with Subscriber; (b) carry out Discovery Education’score business operations; (c) in order to detect, prevent, or investigate security incidents, fraud, and otherabuse or misuse of the Services; (d) identity verification; (e) to comply with Discovery Education’s legalor regulatory obligations; and (f) as otherwise permitted under Applicable Data Protection Laws and inaccordance with the Agreement.

3. Processing of Subscriber Data

3.1 Subscriber Instructions. Subscriber appoints Discovery Education as a Processor to Process SubscriberData on behalf of, and in accordance with, Subscriber’s instructions (a) as set forth in the Agreement andas otherwise necessary to provide the Services to Subscriber (which may include investigating securityincidents, and detecting and preventing exploits or abuse); (b) as necessary to comply with applicablelegal or regulatory obligations, including Applicable Data Protection Laws; and (c) as otherwise agreedin writing between the parties.

3.2 Lawfulness of Instructions. Subscriber will ensure that its instructions comply with Applicable DataProtection Laws. Subscriber acknowledges that Discovery Education is neither responsible fordetermining which laws or regulations are applicable to Subscriber’s business nor whether DiscoveryEducation’s provision of the Services meets or will meet the requirements of such laws or regulations.Subscriber will ensure that Discovery Education’s Processing of Subscriber Data, when done inaccordance with Subscriber’s instructions, will not cause Discovery Education to violate any applicablelaw or regulation, including Applicable Data Protection Laws. Discovery Education will informSubscriber if it becomes aware, or reasonably believes, that Subscriber’s instructions violate anyapplicable law or regulation, including Applicable Data Protection Laws.

3.3 Subscriber shall, in its use of the Services, Process Personal Data in accordance with the requirements ofApplicable Data Protection Laws, including any applicable requirement to provide notice to DataSubjects of the use of Discovery Education as Processor.

3.4 Discovery Education shall:

3.4.1 comply with Applicable Data Protection Laws in the Processing of Subscriber Data;

3.4.2 use Subscriber Data only for the purpose of fulfilling its respective duties and providing theServices under the Agreement; and

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

3

3.4.3 not otherwise Process Subscriber Data other than on Subscriber’s documented instructionsunless Processing is required by Applicable Data Protection Laws to which DiscoveryEducation is subject, in which case Discovery Education shall to the extent permitted byApplicable Data Protection Laws inform Subscriber of that legal requirement before therelevant Processing of that Subscriber Data.

3.5 Subscriber instructs Discovery Education (and authorizes Discovery Education to instruct each Sub-processor) to Process Subscriber Data; and in particular, transfer Subscriber Data to any country orterritory, as reasonably necessary for the provision of the Services and consistent with the Agreement.

4. Discovery Education Personnel

4.1 Confidentiality. Discovery Education shall ensure that its personnel engaged in the Processing ofSubscriber Data are informed of the confidential nature of Subscriber Data, have received appropriatetraining on their responsibilities, and have executed written confidentiality agreements.

4.2 Reliability. Discovery Education shall take commercially reasonable steps to ensure the reliability of itspersonnel engaged in Processing Subscriber Data.

5. Security

5.1 Discovery Education shall maintain appropriate technical and organizational measures to protectSubscriber Data. Subscriber acknowledges that the technical and organizational measures are subject totechnical progress and development and that Discovery Education may update or modify the technicaland organizational measures from time to time, provided that such updates and modifications do notmaterially decrease the overall security of the Services.

6. Sub-processors

6.1 Appointment of Sub-processors. Subscriber acknowledges and agrees that Discovery Education’sAffiliates may be retained as Sub-processors, and Discovery Education and its Affiliates may engageSub-processors in connection with the provision of the Services.

6.2 Sub-processor List. Discovery Education’s current list of Sub-processors engaged in ProcessingPersonal Data for the performance of the Services is available on Discovery Education’s Sub-processorwebpage available at https://www.discoveryeducation.co.uk/subprocessor/. Subscriber consents toDiscovery Education’s use of these Sub-processors.

6.3 Notice. Discovery Education will give Subscriber prior written notice of the appointment of any newSub-processor. Subscriber may object to Discovery Education’s appointment of any new Sub-processorin writing by email to ukprivacy@discoveryed.com within 10 business days of receipt of notice ifSubscriber has reasonable concerns related to such Sub-processor’s ability to comply with ApplicableData Protection Laws. Upon Subscriber’s objection, the parties shall work together in good faith toaddress Subscriber’s concerns. If the parties are unable to reach a resolution, Subscriber may terminatethe applicable Order Form(s) with respect to only those Services that cannot be provided by DiscoveryEducation without the use of the objected-to new Sub-processor by providing written notice to DiscoveryEducation. In such case, Discovery Education will refund Subscriber a pro-rated amount to reflect anyprepaid fees that cover the remainder of the term of such Order Form(s) following the effective date oftermination with respect to such terminated Services.

6.4 Discovery Education will enter into a written agreement with each Sub-processor imposing dataprotection terms that require the Sub-processor to protect Subscriber Data to the standard required byApplicable Data Protection Laws.

7. Data Subject Rights

Taking into account the nature of the Processing, Discovery Education will provide reasonable and timelyassistance (at Subscriber’s expense) to enable Subscriber to respond to any request from a Data Subjectto exercise any of its rights under Applicable Data Protection Laws. Discovery Education shall notifySubscriber about any request it has received directly from a Data Subject without obligation to handle it(unless otherwise agreed or required to do so in order to comply with applicable laws).

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

4

8. Government Access Requests

If Discovery Education receives a legally binding request to access Subscriber Data from a lawenforcement authority or regulator, Discovery Education shall, unless otherwise legally prohibited, givereasonable notice to Subscriber, including a summary of the nature of the request, to allow Subscriber toseek a protective order or other appropriate remedy. To the extent Discovery Education is prohibited bylaw from providing such notification, Discovery Education shall use commercially reasonable efforts toobtain a waiver of the prohibition to enable Discovery Education to communicate as much informationas possible, as soon as possible. Discovery Education will attempt to redirect the law enforcement agencyor regulator to request that data directly from Subscriber. As part of this effort, Discovery Education mayprovide Subscriber’s contact information to the law enforcement agency or regulator. DiscoveryEducation shall not disclose the Subscriber Data requested until required to do so under the applicableprocedural rules. Discovery Education agrees it will provide the minimum amount of informationpermissible when responding to a request for disclosure, based on a reasonable interpretation of therequest. Discovery Education shall promptly notify Subscriber if Discovery Education becomes awareof any direct access by a law enforcement authority or regulator to Subscriber Data and provideinformation available to Discovery Education in this respect, to the extent permitted by law. For theavoidance of doubt, this DPA shall not require Discovery Education to pursue action or inaction thatcould result in civil or criminal penalty for Discovery Education such as contempt of court.

9. Personal Data Breach

9.1 Discovery Education shall notify Subscriber without undue delay upon Discovery Education becomingaware of a Personal Data Breach affecting Subscriber Data.

9.2 In the event of a Personal Data Breach, Discovery Education is not authorized to notify a data protectionor other authority, the Data Subjects concerned, or any other third parties unless Discovery Education isrequired to do so under Applicable Data Protection Laws. In such event, Discovery Education shall, tothe extent permitted under Applicable Data Protection Laws, liaise and coordinate with Subscriber priorto making a notification.

10. Data Protection Impact Assessment and Prior Consultation

Discovery Education shall provide reasonable assistance to Subscriber with any data protection impactassessments and prior consultations with supervisory authorities or other regulatory entities whichSubscriber reasonably considers to be required of Subscriber by any Applicable Data Protection Laws,in each case solely in relation to Processing of Subscriber Data by, and taking into account the nature ofthe Processing and information available to, Discovery Education.

11. Deletion or Return of Subscriber Data

At the choice of Subscriber, Discovery Education will delete or return all Subscriber Data (includingcopies) Processed on behalf of Subscriber; provided that Discovery Education may anonymizeSubscriber Data so that it is no longer personally identifiable and may retain the resulting anonymizeddata. This requirement does not apply to the extent Discovery Education is required by applicable law toretain some or all of the Subscriber Data, or to Subscriber Data it has archived on back-up systems, whichSubscriber Data Discovery Education will securely isolate and protect from any further Processing.

12. Audit

12.1 Subject to subsections 12.2 to 12.4, upon request, Discovery Education will make available to Subscriberall information necessary to demonstrate compliance with this DPA, and shall allow for and contributeto audits, including inspections, by Subscriber or an auditor mandated by Subscriber in relation to theProcessing of the Subscriber Data by Discovery Education. Any audit performed pursuant to this Sectionwill be conducted under a non-disclosure agreement and any information or report derived from suchaudit will be deemed Discovery Education’s Confidential Information. Subscriber cannot exercise thisright more than once per calendar year.

12.2 Upon Subscriber’s request to perform an inspection or audit in accordance with subsection 12.1, to theextent permitted by the Applicable Data Protection Laws, Discovery Education may elect to retain aqualified and independent assessor to perform such inspection or audit, using an appropriate and accepted

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

5

control standard or framework and assessment procedure for such assessments. On the condition thatSubscriber has entered into an applicable non-disclosure agreement with Discovery Education,Discovery Education may supply (on a confidential basis) a summary copy of its audit report toSubscriber; and provide written responses (on a confidential basis) to all reasonable requests forinformation made by Subscriber related to its Processing of Subscriber Data, including responses toinformation security and audit questionnaires, that are necessary t o confirm Discovery Education’scompliance with this DPA.

12.3 Subscriber will give Discovery Education reasonable notice of any audit or inspection to be conductedunder subsection 12.1 and shall make (and ensure that each of its mandated auditors makes) reasonableefforts to avoid causing (or, if it cannot avoid, to minimize) any damage, injury or disruption to DiscoveryEducation’s and/or any Sub-processor’s premises, equipment, personnel, and business while itspersonnel are on those premises in the course of such an audit or inspection. Discovery Education andany Sub-processor(s) need not give access to its premises for the purposes of such an audit or inspection:

12.3.1 to any individual unless they produce reasonable evidence of identity and authority;

12.3.2 outside normal business hours at those premises, unless the audit or inspection needs to beconducted on an emergency basis and Subscriber has given notice to Discovery Educationthat this is the case before attendance outside those hours begins; or

12.3.3 for the purposes of more than one audit or inspection of Discovery Education or any Sub-processor in any calendar year, except for any additional audits or inspections which:

12.3.3.1 Subscriber reasonably considers necessary because of genuine concerns as toDiscovery Education’s compliance with this DPA; or

12.3.3.2 Subscriber is required or requested to carry out by the Applicable DataProtection Laws, a Supervisory Authority, or any similar regulatory authorityresponsible for the enforcement of the Applicable Data Protection Laws inany country or territory,

where Subscriber has identified its concerns or the relevant requirement or request in itsnotice to Discovery Education of the audit or inspection.

12.4 Each party shall bear its own costs with respect to any audit and/or inspection.

13. Transfer Mechanisms for Restricted Transfers

13.1 EEA Restricted Transfers. The Parties acknowledge and agree that to the extent a Party undertakes anEEA Restricted Transfer, the Parties shall Process Subscriber Data which is subject to the EEA RestrictedTransfer in accordance with the Standard Contractual Clauses, appended hereto as Schedule 2.

13.2 UK Restricted Transfers. The Parties acknowledge and agree that to the extent a Party undertakes aUK Restricted Transfer, the parties shall Process Subscriber Data which is subject to the UK RestrictedTransfer in accordance with the UK Addendum, appended hereto as Schedule 3.

13.3 Modules Applicable. The Parties acknowledge and agree that:

13.3.1 Module 1. Where either Party and/or its Authorized Affiliate (acting as a controller)undertakes a Restricted Transfer to the other Party (also acting as a controller), then theParties shall comply with Module 1 of the Standard Contractual Clauses.

13.3.2 Module 2. Where Subscriber and/or its Authorized Affiliate is a Controller and a dataexporter, and Discovery Education is a Processor and data importer in respect of thatSubscriber Data, then the Parties shall comply with Module 2 of the Standard ContractualClauses.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

6

14. General Terms

14.1 Governing law and jurisdiction. This DPA is governed by the laws of the jurisdiction agreed to by theParties as governing the Agreement. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the provisions set out in the StandardContractual Clauses and the UK Addendum shall be governed by, and subject to the jurisdiction of, therelevant law and courts as set forth in the Standard Contractual Clauses and the UK Addendum asapplicable. This DPA is in addition to the rights related to privacy or data security set forth in theAgreement.

14.2 Order of precedence. To the extent: (i) the terms contained in this DPA conflict with those containedin the Agreement, the terms in this DPA shall govern and control to the extent such conflict relates to theProcessing of Subscriber Data; and (ii) the terms contained in the UK Addendum conflict with those inthe Standard Contractual Clauses, the terms in the UK Addendum shall prevail in accordance with theHierarchy provisions therein to the extent the conflict relates to a UK Restricted Transfer.

14.3 Obligations of confidentiality of Subscriber Data Processed pursuant to this DPA shall survivetermination of the Agreement.

14.4 Except to the extent set out in subsection 14.5, it is the express intent of the Parties that any person whois not a party to this DPA has no right, as third party beneficiary, under local legal principle or law, toenforce any term of this DPA, and accordingly nothing contained in this DPA will entitle any person(including, data subjects) other than the parties to this DPA, to any claim, cause of action, remedy orright of any kind whatsoever.

14.5 The Parties agree that a data subject may enforce the terms of the Standard Contractual Clauses and theUK Addendum (as applicable) as provided therein.

14.6 Amendment. This DPA may only be amended by a specific amendment to this DPA signed by bothParties hereto. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the Parties acknowledge that should the EuropeanCommission, or UK Government publish new standard contractual clauses or similar (or amendments tothe existing Standard Contractual Clauses and/or UK Addendum) to address Restricted Transfers, andwhere the Parties determine such new or amended clauses are required to address the RestrictedTransfers, such new or amended clauses will replace the Standard Contractual Clauses and/or UKAddendum attached to this DPA upon either Party’s notification to other Party thereof. All RestrictedTransfers will be thereafter made pursuant to such new or amended clauses.

14.7 Indemnification. Each of the parties (“Indemnifying Party”) agrees to indemnify and hold harmlessthe other party and its officers, employees, directors, and agents (“Indemnified Party”) from, and at theIndemnifying Party’s option defend against, any and all third-party claims, losses, liabilities, damages,costs, and expenses (including attorneys’ fees, consultants’ fees, and court costs) (collectively, “Claims”)arising out of the Indemnifying Party’s (i) violation of an Applicable Data Protection Law; or (ii) breachof any provision of this DPA.

14.8 Term. This DPA, including the Standard Contractual Clauses and the UK Addendum (where applicable),will terminate simultaneously and automatically upon deletion by Discovery Education of SubscriberData Processed on behalf of Subscriber, in accordance with Section 11 of this DPA.

14.9 Changes. Discovery Education reserves the right to change the terms of this DPA from time to time.Such changes will become effective when Discovery Education posts the revised DPA on the DiscoveryEducation website. Subscriber and Users should check the DPA from time to time, as they are bound bythe DPA posted on Discovery Education’s website at the time of access. The Parties agree that this DPAreplaces and supersedes any existing DPA the parties may have previously entered into in connectionwith the Services. The current DPA is available at https://www.discoveryeducation.co.uk/data-processing-addendum/.

14.10 Failure by any Party to enforce any of its rights under this DPA shall not be taken as or deemed to be awaiver of such right.

14.11 If any part, term or provision under this DPA is held to be illegal or unenforceable, the validity orenforceability of the remainder of this DPA will not be affected.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

7

14.12 Execution of this DPA by either Party shall be deemed acceptance and execution by that Party of theSchedules, which are duly incorporated into this DPA.

IN WITNESS WHEREOF, this DPA is entered into and becomes a binding part of the Agreement.

Discovery Education

\_________________________________Signature

\_________________________________Name

\_________________________________Title

\_________________________________Date

Subscriber

\_________________________________Signature

\_________________________________Name

\_________________________________Title

\_________________________________Date

Howard Lewis

Managing Director

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

May 9, 2023

8

Schedule 1

Description of Processing/Transfer

1. List of Parties

Data exporter(s):

Name: The entity identified as Subscriber in the applicable Order Form.

Address: The address for the Subscriber associated with its Discovery Education account.

Contact person’s name, position and contact details: The contact details for the Subscriber associatedwith its Discovery Education account.

Activities relevant to the data transferred under these Clauses: The transfer of Subscriber Data fromdata exporter to data importer in the context of the Agreement.

Signature and date: Execution of the DPA on the Effective Date is deemed execution of these Clauseswhich are incorporated therein.

Role (controller/processor): For the purposes of Module 2, Subscriber is a Controller.

Data importer(s):

Name: Discovery Education Europe Limited

Address: 9 Palace Yard Mews, Bath BA1 2NH United Kingdom

Contact person’s name, position and contact details: Legal Department ukprivacy@discoveryed.com

Activities relevant to the data transferred under these Clauses: Discovery Education is a providerof digital educational services which Processes and transfers Subscriber Data at the instructions of thedata exporter in accordance with the terms of the Agreement.

Signature and date: Execution of the DPA on the Effective Date is deemed execution of these Clauseswhich are incorporated therein.

Role (controller/processor): For the purposes of Module 2, Discovery Education is a Processor.

2. Description of Processing/Transfer

Categories of data subjects whose personal data is transferred

• Employees, contractors, and agents of Subscriber

• Subscriber’s users authorized by Subscriber to use the Services (including administrators, educators,pupils)

• Parents or legal guardians of pupils

Categories of personal data transferred

• Employees, contractors, and agents of Subscriber: first name, last name, business contact information(local authority, school, school address, job title, phone number and email address)

• Subscriber’s users authorized by Subscriber to use the Services (Pupils) (where applicable): first name,middle initial, last name, username (logon ID), password, month and year of birth (DoodleLearning pupilusers only), contact information (email address), ID data (pupil ID, class ID), school, pupil key stage andclass, product usage data, device and connection data, including, but not limited to, IP addresses,

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

9

persistent identifiers, log files, browsing history, search history, and information regarding interactionwith the Discovery Education Services.

• Subscriber’s users authorized by Subscriber to use the Services (Administrators and Educators) (whereapplicable): first name, middle initial, last name, username (logon ID), password, month and year ofbirth (Doodle Learning pupil users only), contact information (school, district, email address, businessaddress, school postcode), ID data (teacher ID, class ID), teacher trade association membership number(such as NAHT membership number), if relevant for a special offer, teacher key stage and class(es),product usage data, device and connection data, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, persistentidentifiers, log files, browsing history, search history, and information regarding interaction with theDiscovery Education Services

• Parents or legal guardians of pupils (where applicable): first name, last name, username (logon ID),password, contact information (email address, phone number, and optionally home address, wherephysical resources are required to be distributed or to process payment information), product usage data,device and connection data, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, persistent identifiers, log files,browsing history, search history, and information regarding interaction with a website or the DiscoveryEducation Services

Sensitive data transferred (if applicable)

Except in the limited circumstances where teachers may be asked to provide their National Association of HeadTeachers trade union membership number to receive a discount for certain Services, Subscriber may not submitspecial categories of Personal Data to the Services.

The frequency of the transfer (e.g., whether the data is transferred on a one-off or continuous basis)

Continuous

Nature of the processing

Subscriber Data will be subject to automated and manual Processing operations by the data importer as necessaryto perform the Services under the Agreement.

Purpose(s) of the data transfer and further processing

To perform Services under the Agreement.

The period for which the personal data will be retained, or, if that is not possible, the criteriaused to determinethat period

Discovery Education may retain Subscriber Data for the purposes described above for the duration of the DPA,and for as long as Discovery Education has a legitimate need to retain the Subscriber Data for the purposes forwhich it was collected or transferred, in accordance with Applicable Data Protection Laws.

For transfers to (sub-) processors, also specify subject matter, nature and duration of the processing

For the subject matter, nature and duration as identified above.

3. Competent Supervisory Authority

The supervisory authority of the EEA country where (i) the data exporter is established; or where (ii) the EUrepresentative of the data exporter is established.

4. Technical and Organisational Security Measures

Discovery Education maintains appropriate technical and organisational security measures for protection of thesecurity, confidentiality and integrity of Subscriber Data, as described in the IT Security Policies applicable to thespecific Services purchased by Subscriber, and set forth in Annex II attached hereto.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

10

Schedule 2

Standard Contractual Clauses(European Commission Implementing Decision (EU) 2021/914 4 June 2021)

SECTION 1

Clause 1

Purpose and scope

(a) The purpose of these standard contractual clauses is to ensure compliance with the requirements ofRegulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on theprotection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement ofsuch data (General Data Protection Regulation) for the transfer of personal data to a third country.

(b) The Parties:

(i) the natural or legal person(s), public authority/ies, agency/ies or other body/ies (hereinafter“entity/ies”) transferring the personal data, as listed in Annex I.A. (hereinafter each “dataexporter”), and

(ii) the entity/ies in a third country receiving the personal data from the data exporter, directly orindirectly via another entity also Party to these Clauses, as listed in Annex I.A. (hereinafter each“data importer”)

have agreed to these standard contractual clauses (hereinafter: “Clauses”).

(c) These Clauses apply with respect to the transfer of personal data as specified in Annex I.B.

(d) The Appendix to these Clauses containing the Annexes referred to therein forms an integral part of theseClauses.

Clause 2

Effect and invariability of the Clauses

(a) These Clauses set out appropriate safeguards, including enforceable data subject rights and effectivelegal remedies, pursuant to Article 46(1) and Article 46 (2)(c) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 and, withrespect to data transfers from controllers to processors and/or processors to processors, standardcontractual clauses pursuant to Article 28(7) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, provided they are notmodified, except to select the appropriate Module(s) or to add or update information in the Appendix.This does not prevent the Parties from including the standard contractual clauses laid down in theseClauses in a wider contract and/or to add other clauses or additional safeguards, provided that they donot contradict, directly or indirectly, these Clauses or prejudice the fundamental rights or freedoms ofdata subjects.

(b) These Clauses are without prejudice to obligations to which the data exporter is subject by virtue ofRegulation (EU) 2016/679.

Clause 3

Third-party beneficiaries

(a) Data subjects may invoke and enforce these Clauses, as third-party beneficiaries, against the dataexporter and/or data importer, with the following exceptions:

(i) Clause 1, Clause 2, Clause 3, Clause 6, Clause 7;

(ii) Clause 8 - Module One: Clause 8.5 (e) and Clause 8.9(b); Module Two: Clause8.1(b), 8.9(a),(c), (d) and (e);

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

11

(iii) Clause 9 - Module Two: Clause 9(a), (c), (d) and (e);

(iv) Clause 12 – Module One: Clause 12(a) and (d); Module Two: Clause 12(a), (d) and (f);

(v) Clause 13;

(vi) Clause 15.1(c), (d) and (e);

(vii) Clause 16(e);

(viii) Clause 18 – Modules One and Two: Clause 18(a) and (b)

(b) Paragraph (a) is without prejudice to rights of data subjects under Regulation (EU)2016/679.

(c)

Clause 4

Interpretation

(a) Where these Clauses use terms that are defined in Regulation (EU) 2016/679, thoseterms shall havethe same meaning as in that Regulation.

(b) These Clauses shall be read and interpreted in the light of the provisions ofRegulation (EU) 2016/679.

(c) These Clauses shall not be interpreted in a way that conflicts with rights andobligations provided for inRegulation (EU) 2016/679.

Clause 5

Hierarchy

In the event of a contradiction between these Clauses and the provisions of related agreementsbetweenthe Parties, existing at the time these Clauses are agreed or entered into thereafter, these Clauses shallprevail.

Clause 6

Description of the transfer(s)

The details of the transfer(s), and in particular the categories of personal data that are transferred and thepurpose(s) for which they are transferred, are specified in Annex I.B.

Clause 7 – Optional

Docking clause

Deliberately omitted.

SECTION 2 - OBLIGATIONS OF THE PARTIES

Clause 8

Data protection safeguards

The data exporter warrants that it has used reasonable efforts to determine that the data importer is able,through the implementation of appropriate technical and organisationalmeasures, to satisfy its obligationsunder these Clauses.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

12

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

8.1 Purpose limitation

The data importer shall process the personal data only for the specific purpose(s) of thetransfer,as set out in Annex I.B. It may only process the personal data for another purpose:

(a) where it has obtained the data subject’s prior consent;

(b) where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims inthe context ofspecific administrative, regulatory or judicial proceedings; or

(c) where necessary in order to protect the vital interests of the data subject or ofanother naturalperson.

8.2 Transparency

(a) In order to enable data subjects to effectively exercise their rights pursuant to Clause 10, thedata importer shall inform them, either directly or through the data exporter:

(i) of its identity and contact details;

(ii) of the categories of personal data processed;

(iii) of the right to obtain a copy of these Clauses;

(iv) where it intends to onward transfer the personal data to any third party/ies, of therecipient or categories of recipients (as appropriate with a view to providingmeaningfulinformation), the purpose of such onward transfer and the ground therefore pursuantto Clause 8.7.

(b) Paragraph (a) shall not apply where the data subject already has the information, including whensuch information has already been provided by the data exporter, or providing the informationproves impossible or would involve a disproportionate effort for the data importer. In the lattercase, the data importer shall, to the extent possible, make the information publicly available.

(c) On request, the Parties shall make a copy of these Clauses, including the Appendixascompleted by them, available to the data subject free of charge. To the extent necessary toprotect business secrets or other confidential information, including personal data, the Partiesmay redact part of the text of the Appendix prior to sharing a copy, but shall provide ameaningful summary where the data subject would otherwise not be able to understand itscontent or exercise his/her rights. On request, the Parties shall provide the data subject with thereasons for the redactions, to the extent possible without revealing the redacted information.

(d) Paragraphs (a) to (c) are without prejudice to the obligations of the data exporter under Articles13 and 14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679.

8.3 Accuracy and data minimisation

(a) Each Party shall ensure that the personal data is accurate and, where necessary, kept up to date.The data importer shall take every reasonable step to ensure that personal data that is inaccurate,having regard to the purpose(s) of processing, is erased or rectified without delay.

(b) If one of the Parties becomes aware that the personal data it has transferred or received isinaccurate, or has become outdated, it shall inform the other Party withoutundue delay.

(c) The data importer shall ensure that the personal data is adequate, relevant and limitedto what isnecessary in relation to the purpose(s) of processing.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

13

8.4 Storage limitation

The data importer shall retain the personal data for no longer than necessary for the purpose(s)for whichit is processed. It shall put in place appropriate technical or organisational measures to ensure compliancewith this obligation, including erasure or anonymisation of the data andall back-ups at the end of theretention period.

8.5 Security of processing

(a) The data importer and, during transmission, also the data exporter shall implement appropriatetechnical and organisational measures to ensure the security of the personal data, includingprotection against a breach of security leading to accidental or unlawful destruction, loss,alteration, unauthorised disclosure or access (hereinafter “personal data breach”). In assessingthe appropriate level of security, they shall take due account of the state of the art, the costs ofimplementation, the nature, scope, context and purpose(s) of processing and the risks involvedin the processing for the data subject. The Parties shall in particular consider having recourse toencryption or pseudonymisation, including during transmission, where the purpose ofprocessing can be fulfilled in that manner.

(b) The Parties have agreed on the technical and organisational measures set out in Annex II. Thedata importer shall carry out regular checks to ensure that these measures continue to providean appropriate level of security.

(c) The data importer shall ensure that persons authorised to process the personal data havecommitted themselves to confidentiality or are under an appropriate statutory obligation ofconfidentiality.

(d) In the event of a personal data breach concerning personal data processed by the dataimporterunder these Clauses, the data importer shall take appropriate measures to address the personaldata breach, including measures to mitigate its possible adverse effects.

(e) In case of a personal data breach that is likely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms ofnatural persons, the data importer shall without undue delay notify both the data exporter andthe competent supervisory authority pursuant to Clause 13. Such notification shall contain i) adescription of the nature of the breach (including, where possible, categories and approximatenumber of data subjects and personaldata records concerned), ii) its likely consequences, iii)the measures taken or proposed to address the breach, and iv) the details of a contact pointfrom whom more information can be obtained. To the extent it is not possible for the dataimporter to provide all the information at the same time, it may do so in phases without unduefurther delay.

(f) In case of a personal data breach that is likely to result in a high risk to the rights and freedomsof natural persons, the data importer shall also notify without undue delay the data subjectsconcerned of the personal data breach and its nature, if necessary in cooperation with the dataexporter, together with the information referred to inparagraph (e), points ii) to iv), unless thedata importer has implemented measures to significantly reduce the risk to the rights orfreedoms of natural persons, or notification would involve disproportionate efforts. In the lattercase, the data importer shall instead issue a public communication or take a similar measure toinform the public of the personal data breach.

(g) The data importer shall document all relevant facts relating to the personal databreach,including its effects and any remedial action taken, and keep a record thereof.

8.6 Sensitive data

Where the transfer involves personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religiousor philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic data, or biometric data for the purpose ofuniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or a person’s sex life or sexual orientation,or data relating to criminal convictions or offences (hereinafter “sensitive data”), the data importer shallapply specific restrictions and/or additional safeguards adapted to the specific nature of the data and therisks involved. This may include restricting the personnel permitted to access the personal data,

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

14

additional security measures (such as pseudonymisation) and/or additional restrictions with respect tofurther disclosure.

8.7 Onward transfers

The data importer shall not disclose the personal data to a third party located outside the European Union(in the same country as the data importer or in another third country, hereinafter “onward transfer”)unless the third party is or agrees to be bound by these Clauses,under the appropriate Module. Otherwise,an onward transfer by the data importer may only take place if:

(a) it is to a country benefitting from an adequacy decision pursuant to Article 45 of Regulation(EU) 2016/679 that covers the onward transfer;

(b) the third party otherwise ensures appropriate safeguards pursuant to Articles 46 or 47 ofRegulation (EU) 2016/679 with respect to the processing in question;

(c) the third party enters into a binding instrument with the data importer ensuring the same levelof data protection as under these Clauses, and the data importer provides a copy of thesesafeguards to the data exporter;

(d) it is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims in the context of specificadministrative, regulatory or judicial proceedings;

(e) it is necessary in order to protect the vital interests of the data subject or of another naturalperson; or

(f) where none of the other conditions apply, the data importer has obtained the explicit consent ofthe data subject for an onward transfer in a specific situation, after having informed him/her ofits purpose(s), the identity of the recipient and the possible risks of such transfer to him/her dueto the lack of appropriate data protection safeguards. In this case, the data importer shall informthe data exporter and, at the request of the latter, shall transmit to it a copy of the informationprovided to the data subject.

Any onward transfer is subject to compliance by the data importer with all the othersafeguards underthese Clauses, in particular purpose limitation.

8.8 Processing under the authority of the data importer

The data importer shall ensure that any person acting under its authority, including aprocessor,processes the data only on its instructions.

8.9 Documentation and compliance

(a) Each Party shall be able to demonstrate compliance with its obligations under these Clauses. Inparticular, the data importer shall keep appropriate documentation of the processing activitiescarried out under its responsibility.

(b) The data importer shall make such documentation available to the competent supervisoryauthority on request.

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

8.1 Instructions

(a) The data importer shall process the personal data only on documented instructions from the data exporter.The data exporter may give such instructions throughout the duration of the contract.

(b) The data importer shall immediately inform the data exporter if it is unable to follow those instructions.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

15

8.2 Purpose limitation

The data importer shall process the personal data only for the specific purpose(s) of the transfer, as setout in Annex I.B, unless on further instructions from the data exporter.

8.3 Transparency

On request, the data exporter shall make a copy of these Clauses, including the Appendix as completedby the Parties, available to the data subject free of charge. To the extent necessary to protect businesssecrets or other confidential information, including the measures describedin Annex II and personal data,the data exporter may redact part of the text of the Appendix tothese Clauses prior to sharing a copy, butshall provide a meaningful summary where the data subject would otherwise not be able to understandthe its content or exercise his/her rights. Onrequest, the Parties shall provide the data subject with thereasons for the redactions, to the extent possible without revealing the redacted information. This Clauseis without prejudice tothe obligations of the data exporter under Articles 13 and 14 of Regulation (EU)2016/679.

8.4 Accuracy

If the data importer becomes aware that the personal data it has received is inaccurate, or has becomeoutdated, it shall inform the data exporter without undue delay. In this case, the data importer shallcooperate with the data exporter to erase or rectify the data.

8.5 Duration of processing and erasure or return of data

Processing by the data importer shall only take place for the duration specified in Annex I.B. After theend of the provision of the processing services, the data importer shall, at the choice of the data exporter,delete all personal data processed on behalf of the data exporter and certify to the data exporter that ithas done so, or return to the data exporter all personal data processed on its behalf and delete existingcopies. Until the data is deleted or returned, thedata importer shall continue to ensure compliance withthese Clauses. In case of local laws applicable to the data importer that prohibit return or deletion of thepersonal data, the data importer warrants that it will continue to ensure compliance with these Clausesand will only process it to the extent and for as long as required under that local law. This is withoutprejudice to Clause 14, in particular the requirement for the data importer under Clause 14(e) to notifythe data exporter throughout the duration of the contract if it has reason to believe that it is or has becomesubject to laws or practices not in line with the requirements under Clause 14(a).

8.6 Security of processing

(a) The data importer and, during transmission, also the data exporter shall implement appropriate technicaland organisational measures to ensure the security of the data, including protection against a breach ofsecurity leading to accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure or accessto that data (hereinafter“personal data breach”). In assessing the appropriate level of security, the Partiesshall take due account of the state of the art, the costs of implementation, the nature, scope, context andpurpose(s) of processing and the risks involved in the processing for the data subjects. The Parties shallin particular consider having recourse to encryption or pseudonymisation, including during transmission,where the purpose ofprocessing can be fulfilled in that manner. In case of pseudonymisation, theadditional information for attributing the personal data to a specific data subjectshall, wherepossible, remain under the exclusive control of the data exporter. In complying with its obligations underthis paragraph, the data importer shall at least implement the technical and organisational measuresspecified in Annex II. The data importer shall carry out regular checks to ensure that these measurescontinue to provide an appropriate level of security.

(b) The data importer shall grant access to the personal data to members of its personnel only to the extentstrictly necessary for the implementation, management and monitoring of the contract. It shall ensurethat persons authorised to process the personal data have committed themselves to confidentiality or areunder an appropriate statutory obligation of confidentiality.

(c) In the event of a personal data breach concerning personal data processed by the dataimporter under theseClauses, the data importer shall take appropriate measures to address the breach, including measures to

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

16

mitigate its adverse effects. The data importer shall also notify the data exporter without undue delayafter having become aware of the breach. Such notification shall contain the details of a contact pointwhere more information can be obtained, a description of the nature of the breach (including, wherepossible, categories and approximate number of data subjects and personal data records concerned), itslikely consequences and the measures taken or proposed to address the breach including, whereappropriate, measures to mitigate itspossible adverse effects. Where, and in so far as, it is notpossible to provide all information at the same time, the initial notification shall contain the informationthen available and further information shall, as it becomes available, subsequently be provided withoutundue delay.

(d) The data importer shall cooperate with and assist the data exporter to enable the data exporter to complywith its obligations under Regulation (EU) 2016/679, in particular to notify the competent supervisoryauthority and the affected data subjects, taking into account the nature of processing and the informationavailable tothe data importer.

8.7 Sensitive data

Where the transfer involves personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religiousor philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic data, or biometric data for the purpose ofuniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or a person’s sex life or sexual orientation,or data relating to criminal convictions and offences (hereinafter“sensitive data”), the data importer shallapply the specific restrictions and/or additional safeguards described in Annex I.B.

8.8 Onward transfers

The data importer shall only disclose the personal data to a third party on documented instructions fromthe data exporter. In addition, the data may only be disclosed to a third partylocated outside the EuropeanUnion (in the same country as the data importer or in another third country, hereinafter “onward transfer”)if the third party is or agrees to be bound by these Clauses, under the appropriate Module, or if:

(i) the onward transfer is to a country benefitting from an adequacy decision pursuant to Article 45of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 that covers the onward transfer;

(ii) the third party otherwise ensures appropriate safeguards pursuant to Articles 46 or 47 Regulationof (EU) 2016/679 with respect to the processing in question;

(iii) the onward transfer is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims in thecontext of specific administrative, regulatory or judicial proceedings; or

(iv) the onward transfer is necessary in order to protect the vital interests of the datasubject or ofanother natural person.

Any onward transfer is subject to compliance by the data importer with all the other safeguards underthese Clauses, in particular purpose limitation.

8.9 Documentation and compliance

(a) The data importer shall promptly and adequately deal with enquiries from the data exporter that relate tothe processing under these Clauses.

(b) The Parties shall be able to demonstrate compliance with these Clauses. In particular,the data importershall keep appropriate documentation on the processing activities carried out on behalf of the dataexporter.

(c) The data importer shall make available to the data exporter all information necessary to demonstratecompliance with the obligations set out in these Clauses and at the data exporter’s request, allow for andcontribute to audits of the processing activities covered by these Clauses, at reasonable intervals or ifthere are indications of non- compliance. In deciding on a review or audit, the data exporter may takeinto accountrelevant certifications held by the data importer.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

17

(d) The data exporter may choose to conduct the audit by itself or mandate an independent auditor. Auditsmay include inspections at the premises or physical facilities of the data importer and shall, whereappropriate, be carried out withreasonable notice.

(e) The Parties shall make the information referred to in paragraphs (b) and (c), including the results of anyaudits, available to the competent supervisory authority on request.

Clause 8

Use of sub-processors

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

(a) The data importer has the data exporter’s general authorisation for the engagement of sub-processor(s)from an agreed list. The data importer shall specifically inform the data exporter in writing of anyintended changes to that list through the addition or replacement of sub- processors at least thirty (30)days in advance, thereby giving the data exporter sufficient time to be able to object to such changesprior to the engagement of the sub-processor(s). The data importer shall provide the data exporter withthe information necessary to enable the data exporter to exercise its right to object.

(b) Where the data importer engages a sub-processor to carry out specific processing activities (on behalf ofthe data exporter), it shall do so by way of a written contract that provides for, in substance, the samedata protection obligations as those binding the data importer under these Clauses, including in terms ofthird-party beneficiary rights for data subjects. The Parties agree that, by complying with this Clause, thedata importer fulfils its obligations under Clause 8.8. The data importer shall ensure that the sub-processor complies with the obligations to which the data importer is subject pursuant to these Clauses.

(c) The data importer shall provide, at the data exporter’s request, a copy of such a sub- processor agreementand any subsequent amendments to the data exporter. To the extent necessary to protect business secretsor other confidential information, including personal data, the data importer may redact the text of theagreement prior to sharing a copy.

(d) The data importer shall remain fully responsible to the data exporter for the performance of the sub-processor’s obligations under its contract with the data importer. The data importer shall notify the dataexporter of any failure by the sub- processor to fulfil its obligations under that contract.

(e) The data importer shall agree a third-party beneficiary clause with the sub-processor whereby - in theevent the data importer has factually disappeared, ceased to exist in law or has become insolvent - thedata exporter shall have the right to terminate the sub-processor contract and to instruct the sub-processorto erase or return the personal data.

Clause 9

Data subject rights

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

(a) The data importer, where relevant with the assistance of the data exporter, shall deal with any enquiriesand requests it receives from a data subject relating to the processing of his/her personal data and theexercise of his/her rights under these Clauses without undue delay and at the latest within one month ofthe receipt of the enquiry or request. The data importer shall take appropriate measures to facilitate suchenquiries, requests and the exercise of data subject rights. Any information provided to the data subjectshall be in an intelligible and easily accessible form, using clear and plain language.

(b) In particular, upon request by the data subject the data importer shall, free of charge:

(i) provide confirmation to the data subject as to whether personal data concerninghim/her is beingprocessed and, where this is the case, a copy of the data relating to him/her and the informationin Annex I; if personal data has been or will be onward transferred, provide information onrecipients or categories of recipients (as appropriate with a view to providing meaningfulinformation) to which the personal data has been or will be onward transferred, the purpose of

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

18

such onward transfers and their ground pursuant to Clause 8.7; and provide information on theright to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in accordance with Clause 12(c)(i);

(ii) rectify inaccurate or incomplete data concerning the data subject;

(iii) erase personal data concerning the data subject if such data is being or has beenprocessed inviolation of any of these Clauses ensuring third-party beneficiary rights, or if the data subjectwithdraws the consent on which the processing is based.

(c) Where the data importer processes the personal data for direct marketing purposes, it shall ceaseprocessing for such purposes if the data subject objects to it.

(d) The data importer shall not make a decision based solely on the automated processing of the personaldata transferred (hereinafter “automated decision”), whichwould produce legal effects concerning thedata subject or similarly significantly affect him / her, unless with the explicit consent of the data subjector if authorised todo so under the laws of the country of destination, provided that such laws lays downsuitable measures to safeguard the data subject’s rights and legitimate interests. In this case, the dataimporter shall, where necessary in cooperation with the data exporter:

(i) inform the data subject about the envisaged automated decision, the envisaged consequencesand the logic involved; and

(ii) implement suitable safeguards, at least by enabling the data subject to contest the decision,express his/her point of view and obtain review by a humanbeing.

(e) Where requests from a data subject are excessive, in particular because of their repetitive character, thedata importer may either charge a reasonable fee taking into account the administrative costs of grantingthe request or refuse to act on therequest.

(f) The data importer may refuse a data subject’s request if such refusal is allowed underthe laws of thecountry of destination and is necessary and proportionate in a democratic society to protect one of theobjectives listed in Article 23(1) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679.

(g) If the data importer intends to refuse a data subject’s request, it shall inform the data subject of the reasonsfor the refusal and the possibility of lodging a complaint with the competent supervisory authority and/orseeking judicial redress.

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

(a) The data importer shall promptly notify the data exporter of any request it has received from a datasubject. It shall not respond to that request itself unless it has been authorised to do so by the data exporter.

(b) The data importer shall assist the data exporter in fulfilling its obligations to respond to data subjects’requests for the exercise of their rights under Regulation (EU) 2016/679. In this regard, the Parties shallset out in Annex II the appropriate technical and organisational measures, taking into account the natureof the processing, by which the assistance shall be provided, as well as the scope and the extent of theassistance required.

(c) In fulfilling its obligations under paragraphs (a) and (b), the data importer shall comply with theinstructions from the data exporter.

Clause 10

Redress

(a) The data importer shall inform data subjects in a transparent and easily accessible format, throughindividual notice or on its website, of a contact point authorised to handle complaints. It shall dealpromptly with any complaints it receives from a data subject.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

19

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

(b) In case of a dispute between a data subject and one of the Parties as regards compliance with theseClauses, that Party shall use its best efforts to resolve the issueamicably in a timely fashion. The Partiesshall keep each other informed about such disputes and, where appropriate, cooperate in resolving them.

(c) Where the data subject invokes a third-party beneficiary right pursuant to Clause 3, the data importershall accept the decision of the data subject to:

(i) lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority in the Member State of his/herhabitualresidence or place of work, or the competent supervisory authority pursuant to Clause 13;

(i) refer the dispute to the competent courts within the meaning of Clause 18.

(d) The Parties accept that the data subject may be represented by a not-for-profit body, organisation orassociation under the conditions set out in Article 80(1) of Regulation(EU) 2016/679.

(e) The data importer shall abide by a decision that is binding under the applicable EU orMember State law.

(f) The data importer agrees that the choice made by the data subject will not prejudice his/her substantiveand procedural rights to seek remedies in accordance with applicable laws.

(a) In case of a dispute between a data subject and one of the Parties as regards compliance with theseClauses, that Party shall use its best efforts to resolve the issueamicably in a timely fashion. The Partiesshall keep each other informed about such disputes and, where appropriate, cooperate in resolving them.

(b) Where the data subject invokes a third-party beneficiary right pursuant to Clause 3, the data importershall accept the decision of the data subject to:

(i) lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority in the Member State of his/herhabitualresidence or place of work, or the competent supervisory authority pursuant to Clause 13;

(ii) refer the dispute to the competent courts within the meaning of Clause 18.

(c) The Parties accept that the data subject may be represented by a not-for-profit body, organisation orassociation under the conditions set out in Article 80(1) of Regulation(EU) 2016/679.

(d) The data importer shall abide by a decision that is binding under the applicable EU orMember State law.

(e) The data importer agrees that the choice made by the data subject will not prejudice his/her substantiveand procedural rights to seek remedies in accordance with applicable laws.

Clause 11

Liability

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

(a) Each Party shall be liable to the other Party/ies for any damages it causes the other Party/ies by anybreach of these Clauses.

(b) Each Party shall be liable to the data subject, and the data subject shall be entitled to receivecompensation, for any material or non-material damages that the Party causes the data subject bybreaching the third-party beneficiary rights under these Clauses. This is without prejudice to the liabilityof the data exporter under Regulation (EU) 2016/679.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

20

(c) Where more than one Party is responsible for any damage caused to the data subject as a result of abreach of these Clauses, all responsible Parties shall be jointly and severally liable and the data subjectis entitled to bring an action in court against any of these Parties.

(d) The Parties agree that if one Party is held liable under paragraph (c), it shall be entitled to claim backfrom the other Party/ies that part of the compensation corresponding to its / their responsibility for thedamage.

(e) The data importer may not invoke the conduct of a processor or sub-processor to avoid its own liability.

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

(b) Each Party shall be liable to the other Party/ies for any damages it causes the other Party/ies by anybreach of these Clauses.

(c) The data importer shall be liable to the data subject, and the data subject shall be entitled to receivecompensation, for any material or non-material damages the data importer or its sub-processor causesthe data subject by breaching the third-party beneficiary rights under these Clauses.

(d) Notwithstanding paragraph (b), the data exporter shall be liable to the data subject, and the data subjectshall be entitled to receive compensation, for any material or non-material damages the data exporter orthe data importer (or its sub-processor) causes the data subject by breaching the third-party beneficiaryrights under these Clauses. This is without prejudice to the liability of the data exporter and, where thedata exporter is a processor acting on behalf of a controller, to the liability of the controller underRegulation (EU) 2016/679 or Regulation (EU) 2018/1725, as applicable.

(e) The Parties agree that if the data exporter is held liable under paragraph (c) for damages caused by thedata importer (or its sub-processor), it shall be entitled to claim back from the data importer that part ofthe compensation corresponding to the data importer’s responsibility for the damage.

(f) Where more than one Party is responsible for any damage caused to the data subject as a result of abreach of these Clauses, all responsible Parties shall be jointly and severally liable and the data subjectis entitled to bring an action in court against any of these Parties.

(g) The Parties agree that if one Party is held liable under paragraph (e), it shall be entitled to claim backfrom the other Party/ies that part of the compensation corresponding to its / their responsibility for thedamage.

(h) The data importer may not invoke the conduct of a sub-processor to avoid its own liability.

Clause 12

Supervision

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

(a) Where the data exporter is established in an EU Member State: The supervisory authority withresponsibility for ensuring compliance by the data exporter withRegulation (EU) 2016/679 as regardsthe data transfer, as indicated in Annex I.C, shall act as competent supervisory authority.

Where the data exporter is not established in an EU Member State, but falls within the territorialscope of application of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 in accordance withits Article 3(2) and hasappointed a representative pursuant to Article 27(1) ofRegulation (EU) 2016/679: The supervisoryauthority of the Member State in which the representative within the meaning of Article 27(1) ofRegulation (EU) 2016/679is established, as indicated in Annex I.C, shall act as competent supervisoryauthority.

Where the data exporter is not established in an EU Member State, but falls within the territorialscope of application of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 in accordance withits Article 3(2) without

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

21

however having to appoint a representative pursuant to Article 27(2) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679:

The supervisory authority of one of the Member States in which the data subjects whose personal data istransferred under these Clauses in relation to the offering of goods or services to them, or whosebehaviour is monitored, are located, as indicated in Annex I.C, shall act as competentsupervisoryauthority.

(b) The data importer agrees to submit itself to the jurisdiction of and cooperate with the competentsupervisory authority in any procedures aimed at ensuring compliance with these Clauses. In particular,the data importer agrees to respond to enquiries, submit to audits and comply with the measuresadopted by the supervisory authority, including remedial and compensatory measures. It shall providethe supervisory authority with written confirmation that the necessary actions have been taken.

SECTION III – LOCAL LAWS AND OBLIGATIONS IN CASE OF ACCESS BY PUBLICAUTHORITIES

Clause 13

Local laws and practices affecting compliance with the Clauses

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

(a) The Parties warrant that they have no reason to believe that the laws and practices in the third country ofdestination applicable to the processing of the personal data by the data importer, including anyrequirements to disclose personal data or measures authorising access by public authorities, prevent thedata importer from fulfilling its obligations under these Clauses. This is based on the understanding thatlaws and practices that respect the essence of the fundamental rights and freedoms and do not exceedwhat is necessary and proportionate in a democratic society to safeguard one of the objectives listed inArticle 23(1) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, are not in contradiction with these Clauses.

(b) The Parties declare that in providing the warranty in paragraph (a), they have taken due account inparticular of the following elements:

(i) the specific circumstances of the transfer, including the length of the processing chain, thenumber of actors involved and the transmission channels used; intended onward transfers; thetype of recipient; the purpose of processing; the categories and format of the transferred personaldata; the economic sector in which the transfer occurs; the storage location of the datatransferred;

(ii) the laws and practices of the third country of destination– including those requiring thedisclosure of data to public authorities or authorising access by such authorities – relevant inlight of the specific circumstances of the transfer, and the applicable limitations and safeguards;

(iii) any relevant contractual, technical or organisational safeguards put in place to supplement thesafeguards under these Clauses, including measures applied during transmission and to theprocessing of the personal data in the country of destination.

(c) The data importer warrants that, in carrying out the assessment under paragraph (b),it has made its bestefforts to provide the data exporter with relevant information and agrees that it will continue to cooperatewith the data exporter in ensuring compliance with these Clauses.

(d) The Parties agree to document the assessment under paragraph (b) and make it available to the competentsupervisory authority on request.

(e) The data importer agrees to notify the data exporter promptly if, after having agreed to these Clauses andfor the duration of the contract, it has reason to believe that it is or has become subject to laws or practicesnot in line with the requirements under paragraph (a), including following a change in the laws of thethird country or a measure (such as a disclosure request) indicating an application of such laws in practicethat is not in line with the requirements in paragraph (a).

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

22

(f) Following a notification pursuant to paragraph (e), or if the data exporter otherwise has reason to believethat the data importer can no longer fulfil its obligations under these Clauses, the data exporter shallpromptly identify appropriate measures (e.g. technical or organisational measures to ensure security andconfidentiality) to be adopted by the data exporter and/or data importer to address the situation. The dataexporter shall suspend the data transfer if it considers that no appropriate safeguards for such transfer canbe ensured, or if instructed by the competent supervisory authority to do so. In this case, the data exportershall be entitled to terminate the contract, insofar as it concerns the processing of personal data underthese Clauses. If the contract involves more than two Parties, the data exporter may exercise this right totermination only with respect to the relevant Party, unless the Parties have agreed otherwise. Where thecontract is terminated pursuant to this Clause, Clause 16(d) and (e) shall apply.

Clause 14

Obligations of the data importer in case of access by public authorities

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

14.1 Notification

(a) The data importer agrees to notify the data exporter and, where possible, the data subject promptly (ifnecessary with the help of the data exporter) if it:

(i) receives a legally binding request from a public authority, including judicial authorities, underthe laws of the country of destination for the disclosure of personal data transferred pursuant tothese Clauses; such notification shallinclude information about the personal data requested, therequesting authority,the legal basis for the request and the response provided; or

(ii) becomes aware of any direct access by public authorities to personal data transferred pursuantto these Clauses in accordance with the laws of the country of destination; such notificationshall include all information available to the importer.

(b) If the data importer is prohibited from notifying the data exporter and/or the data subject under the lawsof the country of destination, the data importer agrees to useits best efforts to obtain a waiver of theprohibition, with a view to communicating asmuch information as possible, as soon as possible. The dataimporter agrees to document its best efforts in order to be able to demonstrate them on request of the dataexporter.

(c) Where permissible under the laws of the country of destination, the data importer agrees to provide thedata exporter, at regular intervals for the duration of thecontract, with as much relevant information aspossible on the requests received (in particular, number of requests, type of data requested, requestingauthority/ies, whether requests have been challenged and the outcome of such challenges, etc.).

(d) The data importer agrees to preserve the information pursuant to paragraphs (a) to (c)for the duration ofthe contract and make it available to the competent supervisory authority on request.

(e) Paragraphs (a) to (c) are without prejudice to the obligation of the data importer pursuant to Clause 14(e)and Clause 16 to inform the data exporter promptly where itis unable to comply with these Clauses.

14.2 Review of legality and data minimisation

(a) The data importer agrees to review the legality of the request for disclosure, in particular whether itremains within the powers granted to the requesting public authority, and to challenge the request if, aftercareful assessment, it concludes that there are reasonable grounds to consider that the request is unlawfulunder the laws of the country of destination, applicable obligations under international law andprinciples of international comity. The data importer shall, under the same conditions, pursuepossibilities of appeal. When challenging a request, the dataimporter shall seek interim measures with aview to suspending the effects of the request until the competent judicial authority has decided on itsmerits. It shall not disclose the personal data requested until required to do so under the applicable

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

23

procedural rules. These requirements are without prejudice to the obligations of the data importer underClause 14(e).

(b) The data importer agrees to document its legal assessment and any challenge to the request for disclosureand, to the extent permissible under the laws of the country of destination, make the documentationavailable to the data exporter. It shall also makeit available to the competent supervisory authority onrequest.

(c) The data importer agrees to provide the minimum amount of information permissiblewhen respondingto a request for disclosure, based on a reasonable interpretation of the request.

SECTION IV – FINAL PROVISIONS

Clause 15

Non-compliance with the Clauses and termination

(a) The data importer shall promptly inform the data exporter if it is unable to comply with these Clauses,for whatever reason.

(b) In the event that the data importer is in breach of these Clauses or unable to comply with these Clauses,the data exporter shall suspend the transfer of personal data to thedata importer until compliance is againensured or the contract is terminated. This is without prejudice to Clause 14(f).

(c) The data exporter shall be entitled to terminate the contract, insofar as it concerns theprocessing ofpersonal data under these Clauses, where:

(i) the data exporter has suspended the transfer of personal data to the data importer pursuant toparagraph (b) and compliance with these Clauses is not restored within a reasonable time andin any event within one month of suspension;

(ii) the data importer is in substantial or persistent breach of these Clauses; or

(iii) the data importer fails to comply with a binding decision of a competent court or supervisoryauthority regarding its obligations under these Clauses.

In these cases, it shall inform the competent supervisory authority of such non-compliance. Where thecontract involves morethan two Parties, the data exporter may exercise this right to termination only withrespect to the relevant Party, unless the Parties have agreed otherwise.

(d) For Modules One and Two: Personal data that has been transferred prior to the termination of thecontract pursuant to paragraph (c) shall at the choice of the data exporter immediately be returned to thedata exporter or deleted in its entirety. The same shall apply to any copies of the data.

(e) Either Party may revoke its agreement to be bound by these Clauses where (i) the European Commissionadopts a decision pursuant to Article 45(3) of Regulation(EU) 2016/679 that covers the transfer ofpersonal data to which these Clauses apply;or (ii) Regulation (EU) 2016/679 becomes part of the legalframework of the country to which the personal data is transferred. This is without prejudice to otherobligations applying to the processing in question under Regulation (EU) 2016/679.

Clause 16

Governing law

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

These Clauses shall be governed by the law of one of the EU Member States, provided such law allows for third-party beneficiary rights. The Parties agree that this shall be the law of Ireland.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

24

Clause 17

Choice of forum and jurisdiction

MODULE ONE: Transfer controller to controller

MODULE TWO: Transfer controller to processor

(a) Any dispute arising from these Clauses shall be resolved by the courts of an EU Member State.

(b) The Parties agree that those shall be the courts of Ireland.

(c) A data subject may also bring legal proceedings against the data exporter and/or data importer before thecourts of the Member State in which he/she has his/her habitual residence.

(d) The Parties agree to submit themselves to the jurisdiction of such courts.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

25

Annexes I – III to the EU Standard Contractual Clauses (Schedule 2)

Annex I

The details of data transfers are set out in Schedule 1 of the DPA.

Annex II – Technical and Organisational Measures

Purpose. This Annex II describes Discovery Education’s security program, and physical, technical,organizational, and administrative controls and measures to protect Subscriber Data from unauthorized access,destruction, use, modification, or disclosure (the “Security Measures”). Unless otherwise specified, the SecurityMeasures apply to Discovery Education Experience, Espresso, Coding, Health \& Relationships, STEM Connect,and DoodleLearning.

Definitions. Any capitalized terms used but not defined in this document have the meanings set out in theAgreement or DPA.

Discovery Education has implemented the following Security Measures:

1. Organizational Measures.a. Discovery Education has a designated security officer responsible for overseeing its securityprogram.b. Information security personnel are trained and qualified.c. Information security training and awareness is conducted and provided to DiscoveryEducation employees.2. Access and Management Controls. Discovery Education implements procedures designed to limitpersonnel’s access to Subscriber Data as follows:a. Limits internal access to Subscriber Data, applications, and systems to Discovery Educationpersonnel with proper authorization and allow use and/or disclosure internally, when necessary,solely to personnel based on legitimate business need.b. Revokes access to personnel who no longer require access.c. Requires use of strong passwords or pass phrases.d. Logically separates Subscriber Data and maintains measures designed to prevent SubscriberData from access by other users.e. Restricts access to Discovery Education proprietary source code to prevent unauthorized access.3. Network Security, Physical Security and Environmental Controls. Discovery Education implementsnetwork security, physical security and environmental controls as follows:a. Network intrusion detection and network intrusion prevention technology.b. Physical access controls to processing premises and facilities, provisioning access to theprocessing facilities on the basis of the role (need to know), and utilizing physical AccessControl Mechanisms such as Electronic Access Control (EAC) cards to access server rooms,install CCTV systems, etc.c. For remote access connections, requires multifactor authentication and the use of a VPNconnection for certain personnel to certain systems and applications.d. Properly configured and patched firewalls, network access controls and other technicalmeasures designed to prevent unauthorized access to systems processing Subscriber Data.e. Perform routine maintenance to ensure operating systems and applications are patched andupdated.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

26

f. Monitors security release information for software. Discovery Education prioritizes the rolloutof patches based on the severity or impact of the vulnerability.g. Process for monitoring, alerting, and responding to suspicious activity occurring in theDiscovery Education infrastructure.h. Discovery Education Services operate on Amazon Web Services (AWS) and is protected byAmazon’s security and environmental controls.i. Subscriber Data hosted in AWS is encrypted at rest and in transit. AWS does not have accessto unencrypted Subscriber Data.4. Operating System Security. Discovery Education implements operating security controls as follows:a. Operating systems are protected with anti-malware/virus protection software.b. Server and cloud operating systems are deployed using a secure build process.c. Security logging is enabled per vendor recommendations for all desktop, server, and networkinfrastructure OS.d. Supported operating system versions.e. Anti-virus signatures are updated regularly.5. Data Encryption and Pseudonymisation. Discovery Education implements data encryption andpseudonymization as follows:a. Implements encryption in transport and at rest.b. Implements pseudonymization of Subscriber Data, where appropriate.c. Uses industry standard encryption methodologies to protect Subscriber Data.d. Implements full-disk encryption for hard-drives on personnel workstations.e. External data transmissions of Subscriber Data are encrypted using industry standard securityprotocols.6. Incident Response.a. Discovery Education maintains an information security incident response plan that is tested atleast annually.b. Discovery Education implements and maintains technology designed to detect suspiciousactivity, malicious activity, vulnerabilities and security incidents within Discovery Education’snetwork and systems.7. Vulnerability Management. Discovery Education maintains the following vulnerability managementprocesses for devices used to connect to the Discovery Education network:a. Discovery Education will employ industry standards and tools to conduct routine infrastructurevulnerability scanning to test Discovery Education’s network and application penetration testingof the Discovery Education Services. The results are triaged by the information security team.b. Discovery Education has processes in place designed to ensure adherence to industry standardsecurity development practices for development and testing for code, APIs, and applicationsdeployed and implemented in support of the Discovery Education Services.8. Monitoring and Logging.

a. Discovery Education has implemented procedures to log and regularly review records ofinformation systems activity, including maintaining access logs, access reports, securityincident tracking reports, and periodic access audits.b. Discovery uses a variety of approaches and technologies to make sure that risks and incidentsare appropriately detected, assessed and mitigated on an ongoing basis.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

27

9. Business Continuity Management.a. Discovery Education maintains a business continuity and disaster recovery plan.b. Discovery Education maintains processes to ensure failover redundancy with its systems,networks and data storage.10. Personnel Management.a. For U.S. Discovery Education employees, Discovery Education performs employmentverification, including proof of identity validation, check of education records and employmenttrack, and criminal background checks for new hires in positions requiring access to systemsand applications storing Subscriber Data in accordance with applicable law. For non-U.S.Discovery Education employees, Discovery Education will use commercially reasonable effortsto meet the same criteria as established for U.S.-based Discovery Education employees, subjectto general business practices in the respective country and in compliance with applicable locallaw requirements.b. Upon employee termination, whether voluntary or involuntary, Discovery Educationimmediately disables all access to Discovery Education systems and physical facilities.

Updates and Modifications. The Security Measures are subject to technical progress and development.Discovery Education may update or modify the Security Measures from time to time, provided that such updatesand modifications do not materially decrease the overall security of the Services.

Annex III – List of Sub-processors

Discovery Education’s current list of Sub-processors can be found athttps://www.discoveryeducation.co.uk/subprocessor/.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC

28

Schedule 3

International Data Transfer Addendum to the EU Commission Standard Contractual Clauses (the“Addendum”) (Version B1.0, in force 21 March 2022)

Part 1: Tables

Start date Effective Date of the DPA

The Parties Exporter (who sends the RestrictedTransfer)Importer (who receives the RestrictedTransfer)

Parties’ details See Schedule 2, Annex 1(1), of the

DPA

See Schedule 2, Annex 1(1), of the

DPA

Key Contact See Schedule 2, Annex 1(1), of the

DPA

See Schedule 2, Annex 1(1), of the

DPA

Signature (if requiredfor the purposes ofSection 2)

Execution of the DPA on the Effective

Date is deemed execution of thisAddendum

Execution of the DPA on the EffectiveDate is deemed execution of thisAddendum

Table 2: Selected SCCs, Modules and Selected Clauses

Addendum EU SCCs The version of the Approved EU SCCs which this Addendum is appended to,

detailed below, including the Appendix Information:Date: Effective Date of DPAReference (if any): NoneOther identifier (if any): None

Table 3: Appendix Information

“Appendix Information” means the information which must be provided for the selected modules as set out inthe Appendix of the Approved EU SCCs (other than the Parties), and which for this Addendum is set out in:Annex 1(1) – (3) A: List of Parties: See Schedule 2, Annex 1, of the DPA

Annex 1(1) – (3) B: Description of Transfer: See Schedule 2, Annex 1, of the DPA

Annex II: Technical and organisational measures including technical and organisational measures to ensure thesecurity of the data: See Schedule 2, Annex II, of the DPA

Annex III: List of Sub-processors (Module 2 only): See Schedule 2, Annex III, of the DPA

Table 4: Ending this Addendum when the Approved Addendum Changes

Ending thisAddendum whenthe ApprovedAddendumchanges

Which Parties may end this Addendum as set out in Section 19:

☐ Importer

X Exporter

☐ neither Party

PART 2: MANDATORY CLAUSES

Mandatory Clauses of the Approved Addendum, being the template Addendum B.1.0 issued by the ICO and laidbefore Parliament in accordance with s119A of the Data Protection Act of 2019 on 2 February 2022, as it isrevised under Section 18 of those Mandatory Clauses.

DocuSign Envelope ID: 3890E517-70A7-4DC0-83CF-77B64FCFFFBC
